

ABBY WYSOPAL

ADAPTABLE ~ DRIVEN ~ CONSIDERATE

CONTACT

HOME ADDRESS

2239 Aralia Street

Newport Beach, CA 92660

EMAIL

abbywysopal@gmail.com

CELL PHONE NUMBER

(949) 413-1533

GITHUB

https://github.com/abby-wysopal

SKILLS

Computer Programming
Creative and Innovative
Management
Customer Service
Digital Marketing

PROGRAMMING



AWARDS & HONORS

UCSB COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING HONORS – 2019-2020

Maintain a cumulative grade point average above a 3.5 on a 4.0 scale

PRESIDENTIAL VOLUNTEER SERVICE AWARD - 2014-2017

Over 250 hours of cumulative community service hours in a 12 month period

---- PROFILE

Skilled programmer and complex problem-solver experienced in data analytics and report writing. Effective at supporting team needs with high-quality code, subject matter expertise and collaboration skills. While also being a resilient professional well-known for successfully taking problematic customer accounts and turning them into ongoing, lucrative contracts. Pursuing a role where hard work and dedication will be highly valued.

--- EDUCATION ----

- * 3.77 GPA
- University of California, Santa Barbara
- * Bachelor of Science in Engineering: Computer Science, 2021
- * Master of Science in Engineering: Computer Science, 2022

---- COURSEWORK -----

- Operating Systems
- Data Structures and Algorithms
- * Computer Communication Networks
- * Object Oriented Design and Implementation
- * Computer Architecture, Computer Organization, and Logic Design

---- EXPERIENCE

SYSTEM MANAGER

IN 2017 - 2020

JSW ENTERPRISES

- * Served as the web developer and designer. Employed search engine optimization tactics to increase reach of targeted audience and implemented of Google-based campaigns.
- * Delivered a high level of service to clients, including cold calling, networking, marketing, lead generation and account servicing.

INTERN IN 2017

TRANSCEPTA LLC

- * Established open and professional relationships with team members which facilitated communication, quickly resolving issues and conflicts.
- * Collaborated with the IT team and other support staff to develop new applications.

TREASURER IN 2019 - 2020

DELTA GAMMA FRATERNITY

- * Reconciled accounts and investigated variances.
- * Produced Monthly Finance reports outlining the latest financial information such as expenses, income and outstanding balances.
- * Provided extensive clerical and administrative support to department staff.

---- PROJECTS

MAGIC MINUTES

* Lead a team project in creating a ReactJS web interface and iOS application that displays predictive wait times for a theme park.